For seven elite profilers, finding a serial killer is
a process of elimination. Their own.
Mindhunters is a mystery, thriller, crime film directed by Renny Harlin.
Trainees in the FBI's psychological profiling program must put their
training into practice when they discover a killer in their midst.
Based very loosely on Agatha Christie's And Then There Were None.
Sara Moore, played by Kathryn Morris.
Lucas Harper, played by Jonny Lee Miller.
Gabe Jensen, played by LL Cool J.
J.D. Reston, played by Christian Slater.
Nicole Willis, played by Patricia Velásquez.
Vince Sherman, played by Clifton Collins Jr..
Mindhunters is a 2004 crime slasher film directed by Renny Harlin and starring Kathryn Morris, LL Cool J,
Jonny Lee Miller, Patricia Velásquez, Clifton Collins Jr., Christian Slater, and Val Kilmer.
It was written by Wayne Kramer and Kevin Brodbin with
an uncredited rewrite by Ehren Kruger.
Unusually, the last country to receive this film was the United States in 2005, because of the
film's distribution rights being changed from 20th Century Fox to Dimension Films.
In the film, a group of FBI profilers in training are tasked
with tracking a serial killer to pass their exam.
But they find themselves targeted by an actual killer.
The team suspect that one of their members is their enemy, hiding among them.
The film explores themes of island, fbi, simulation, training, serial killer.
The tone is mind_bending and intense.